

_About Me

Innovative, Creative and Enthusiastic, I have spent the last 5 years working in Website Development and Design for various companies and friends. I pride myself on the ability to pick up and learn new programming languages and frameworks quickly and efficiently. In part this is down to the fact that in my spare time I schedule in regular self development to learn new, and improve on existing skills. That way I can always make sure that I am up to date with the latest technologies.

_Skills



Other Skills:

| HTML | HapiJS | HapiJS Express | |
|--------|-------------|----------------|--------|
| jQuery | Material UI | | Smarty |
| Regex | | | |

_Contact Me

Threshings, Dorchester Road, Yeovil, Somerset, BA22 9RD

07847297004

CallumBW@gmail.com







Callum Bridgford-Whittick

Web Developer



Job Experience

Teapot Creative

July 2015 - Current

PrestaShop, WordPress, and Support Developer

I have a deep understanding of PrestaShop front end and back office. Whilst working on the Support Desk I managed tickets varying from requests to bug fixes. I had to resolve issues regarding security, general front end and checkout functionality. When extending existing and creating new functionality I had to understand the clients needs, and consider the feasibility of achieving this within their budget. I also had to undertake client meetings in and outside of the office. I also attend weekly team meetings to plan the week ahead, and discuss any points from the previous week. I have attended various team building exercises that taught us to extrapolate data from situations and analyse situations quickly and efficiently.

This has taught me the following:

- Understanding of MVC; PrestaShop Symfony.
- Understanding of Template based views; Smarty, Twig.
- jQuery, which was later swapped for ECMAScript 6.
- Integration of various Payment Gateways.

Whilst supporting the WordPress Team and creating additional functionality and front end features I learned the following:

- How to use and utilise the API to create a headless CMS.
- Create my own API routes.
- Create a React front end for WordPress.
- Understanding of jQuery and how it can be utilised on the front end.

Jonny Pardoe

January 2019 - Current

Freelance Branding, Website and Video editing

I created a brand for Jonny Pardoe that influenced the design of his website and later his videos. I offer continued support to the website, and continue to create his videos which are posted online to YouTube.

Web Choice UK

June 2014 - April 2015

Junior Developer

Whilst at WebChoice UK I was utilised in a range of roles:

- Project Management.
- Assisting the Lead Salesman as the Technical Advisor in the procuring of one of the companies largest clients; UBL Banks
- Updating the Company Website.

血

Education

The City of Bath College

BTEC National Diploma Level 3

The Corsham School

10 GCSE's C and above